这个手臂三级烧伤
Third-degree burns on this arm.
-有头部创伤吗  -我呼叫了卡洛西科
- Head trauma? - I paged Koracick.
他很忙  发生了什么
And he's busy. What happened?
布雷德摔在他吉他上了  吉他掉在地铁道上
Brad fell on his guitar, which fell on the train tracks.
他当时正在跟女朋友亲热
He was making out with his girlfriend.
两个手腕上都没有脉搏
I don't have a pulse in either wrist,
这个胳膊又冰又硬
and this arm is cold and tight.
-这只也是  -右腿没问题
- This one, too. - Okay, right leg's okay,
但是左脚没有任何反应
but I'm not getting anything in the left foot.
-筋膜室综合症  -筋膜室综合症
- Compartment syndrome. - Compartment syndrome.
手术刀和无菌手套
Scalpels and sterile gloves!
西姆斯  你做过筋膜切开术吗
Simms, you ever done a fasciotomy?
给尸体做过算吗
Does a cadaver count?
你和乔做胳膊  我做腿
You and Jo take the arms. I'll take the leg.
瞳孔相同有反应
Pupils are equal and reactive,
但我不能排除头部受伤
but I can't rule out a head injury.
他需要CT  尽快
He needs a CT ASAP.
等我们拯救他的手脚再说
After we save his limbs.
等我数完就开始做筋膜切开术
Okay, fasciotomies on my count.